[
  {
    "front": ".ajaxComplete()",
    "back": "Register a handler to be called when Ajax requests complete. This is an Ajax Event."
  },
  {
    "front": ".ajaxError()",
    "back": "Register a handler to be called when Ajax requests complete with an error. This is an Ajax Event."
  },
  {
    "front": ".ajaxSend()",
    "back": "Attach a function to be executed before an Ajax request is sent. This is an Ajax Event."
  },
  {
    "front": ".ajaxStart()",
    "back": "Register a handler to be called when the first Ajax request begins. This is an Ajax Event."
  },
  {
    "front": ".ajaxStop()",
    "back": "Register a handler to be called when all Ajax requests have completed. This is an Ajax Event."
  },
  {
    "front": ".ajaxSuccess()",
    "back": "Attach a function to be executed whenever an Ajax request completes successfully. This is an Ajax Event."
  },
  {
    "front": "jQuery.param()",
    "back": "Create a serialized representation of an array or object, suitable for use in a URL query string or Ajax request."
  },
  {
    "front": ".serialize()",
    "back": "Encode a set of form elements as a string for submission."
  },
  {
    "front": ".serializeArray()",
    "back": "Encode a set of form elements as an array of names and values."
  },
  {
    "front": "jQuery.ajax()",
    "back": "Perform an asynchronous HTTP (Ajax) request."
  },
  {
    "front": "jQuery.ajaxSetup()",
    "back": "Set default values for future Ajax requests."
  },
  {
    "front": "jQuery.get()",
    "back": "Load data from the server using a HTTP GET request."
  },
  {
    "front": "jQuery.getJSON()",
    "back": "Load JSON-encoded data from the server using a GET HTTP request."
  },
  {
    "front": "jQuery.getScript()",
    "back": "Load a JavaScript file from the server using a GET HTTP request, then execute it."
  },
  {
    "front": ".load()",
    "back": "Load data from the server and place the returned HTML into the matched element."
  },
  {
    "front": "jQuery.post()",
    "back": "Load data from the server using a HTTP POST request."
  }
]
